Detecting spatial distortion!
What? They're trying to warp here?
Short-distance warp incoming.
Estimating coordinates.
Aim all cannons at the coordinates,
and open fire as soon as
the enemy ship appears.
Warp gate probabilities converging.
Captain! The coordinates!
What about them?
They're close! Way too close!
No way...
Are they suicidal?!
It's not a ship!
It's a mobile knight!
What?!
It can't be...
That's the Plundering Count
and his Black Titan!
All by himself? Open fire!
Weak, you're too weak! Can you
at least make this a little interesting?
You weaklings exist to be my prey.
Fight for your lives and fulfill your purpose!
Master, are you all right?
I am. Impressive as always, Amagi.
You planned this perfectly.
I got to warp out
in the best possible position.
I was right to let you handle the projections.
Your words honor me.
Now, I've personally set the table.
Show me what the rest of you can do.
As you wish, Master.
Time to have some fun.
Attention, all ships.
Proceed at level-three combat speed.
Open fire as soon as you enter combat range.
All mobile knights are to mobilize.
Follow Master Liam's orders.
Christiana moving out. Requesting guidance.
Detecting gravity waves in the battlefield.
Warp success rates plummeting.
It matters not.
I would risk it all to guard Lord Liam.
Plotting cross-dimensional detour
around distortion.
Staggering your warp as much as possible.
Please fight through
the downturn in probability.
Commencing guidance.
Initiating warp drive sequence!
Warp!
You were nothing!
You're late, Tia!
I'm terribly sorry, Lord Liam!
I, Christiana, will get rid of
these insolent scrubs for you!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm saying I'll get rid of them all
if you take your sweet time.
I, Christiana,
will fight proudly alongside you!
The enemy battleships are
now within firing range.
Fire all main cannons at
the enemy battleships.
Enemy ships destroyed.
How do you like the Seventh
Weapons Factory's battleship?
It's got best-in-class
features and performance.
We're in the middle of a battle.
Save it for later, Nias.
But I wanted to hear what you thought already.
If you like it, you could order
another hundred... no, 200 ships?
We would really appreciate your patronage.
Ugh, what a pain.
Amagi, place the orders
and get her out of my face.
As you wish.
Thank you for your purchase!
Sheesh.
Anyway, the fun's just getting started.
What, is this all you've got?
Don't you have anyone stronger?
This is fun! So much fun!
Nothing beats the moment of
crushing the weak without mercy!
It shows me that I am strong—
that I stand alone at the summit of evil!
You can all kneel before me,
the Evil Lord Liam!
Revenge... This is my revenge.
All of it, just to exact
revenge upon my past life!
Yeah... My past life?
It was deplorable and pathetic.
I'm home.
Welcome home, honey.
Thanks, Mika.
Where's Kanami?
She's asleep.
She kept begging for a dog.
Why a dog?
She saw a Shiba at her friend's place.
Now she insists we should get one.
Oh... I don't know if
we could afford one right now.
A dog, huh?
This is nice. You don't get too many days off.
I wanted to come see the dogs myself.
Wow. Do you want to get one too?
Nah, I had one before that
was like family to me.
I still can't bring myself to forget it.
You love with all your heart, huh?
Besides, having you and
Kanami in my life is plenty.
And a dog would cause even
more work for you than we do?
I mean it'd be another family member to love.
I have a wife and daughter I love.
With them, I can live happy and fight
through any and all difficulties...
That's what I thought back then.
I told you to keep me in the damn loop!
You did, and I did send you
a message at once.
Well, I didn't get it, you oaf!
How are you gonna fix this?!
You should know better, Team Lead.
The chief always hits the club on Thursdays.
No point waiting on his approval.
But still...
This guy never learns.
The company I worked at
was toxic and exploitative.
My awful boss worked me like a dog,
and my subordinates openly mocked me.
They'd take credit for things I did...
and blame me for mistakes I didn't make.
Even through all that, my family
gave me the strength to keep going.
I ran myself into the ground working,
and it was all to keep my family happy.
And yet...
Nitta
Nitta-kun?
"Senpai, you know the upcoming
Deluxe Ultra Alloy Majin Gunder?
It's got 3D naval battle add-ons for
the first time! It's finally complete!
You gotta buy it," huh?
Nitta-kun never changes. That's great.
He really does love this stuff.
Is this the right place?
Cafe
3 mins
slower
I'm not familiar with this area.
Mika?
Isn't she supposed to take Kanami
to her sports club today?
Wait, who's that guy?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You're home early.
Yeah.
Let me warm up your dinner for you.
How was today?
What do you mean?
Kanami's sports club.
Kanami won a sword fighting match today.
Right, Kanami?
Yep!
Hi-yah!
Whoa!
You won, huh? I'm proud of ya, Kanami.
Hey, Mika. Today...
What?
Never mind. It's nothing.
Come on. Don't be weird.
Yeah, it's nothing.
I just misunderstood.
Mika would never be unfaithful.
Yeah.
Not Mika, of all people...
Not again.
What's wrong?
I can't put the PC to sleep.
I gotta step out, too.
Guess you'll have to save
your work and shut it down.
Shut down
Reboot
Yeah, that's right.
Just got here.
Yeah, I'm with Kanami. Where are you?
I see him over there!
I see you now. Let's go, Kanami.
Yeah... Papa!
Why did she call another man "Papa"?
No... It can't be.
That must've been a friend.
A friend who's playing her father
because I'm always too busy with work.
Yeah, that's gotta be it.
What are you slacking off for?
I'm sorry. My PC's just acting up.
It takes a while to wake up from sleep.
Then don't put it to sleep.
But I have to when I go on break
for security reasons.
Then don't go on break.
Just hurry up and get to it.
Right.
Mika
Sorry, Mika, I'm still working.
Bad news! Kanami's been in an accident!
Kanami?!
How is she?
Operating
In surgery...
Are you Kanami-chan's parents?
Yes.
She needs a transfusion.
Can you donate your blood?
Of course!
What are your blood types?
I'm AB-positive.
I'm O-positive.
Ma'am, if you would.
What about me?
Kanami-chan's an O, so it has to be her.
Mother's Blood Type
Father's Blood Type
Why the hell is Kanami an O?
Is the father...
What is the meaning of this?!
Who's the father?
Is Kanami not my child?!
Say something, damn it!
What are you talking about?
It's too late for all this.
Too late, my foot!
I tried so hard not to ask!
You seem to be misunderstanding something.
What?
I was the one trying hard not to lash out.
You don't care one bit about our family.
You work overtime every day
and even go on weekends.
You only come here to sleep.
No time to even have a conversation.
You may as well not exist in this home.
What do you expect? It's my job.
And what good is this job?
What are you...
You can't climb the ladder,
you don't get any raises,
you get pennies for bonuses,
and we hardly have savings.
Kanami needs a good quality education,
and we can't give her one with our finances.
So don't you act like
your job means anything!
Wha...
You promised me happiness
if I married you, remember?
Well, it's been more than ten years.
How much time in those ten-plus years
have you graced me with your presence?
Well...
While you were never here,
I did the housework, raised a child,
and lived basically all by myself!
Hngh
But that's your...
Yeah, that's my job!
And all those times have been
Kanami's and mine alone!
And this is Kanami's and my life,
just the two of us!
You're not a part of this home.
I'm going to take Kanami and leave.
And go where?
Kanami
Do you have to ask?
Kanami.
Let's go to Papa.
Wait!
Move.
I said wait!
And I said move.
Wait just a damn minute!
Move!
You think you can just
leave and that'll be that?
Oh, that will be that.
What do you care about Kanami?
I've raised her all this time!
How could I not care?!
I'm the one who raised her.
You were never around.
I was! I was right here!
Right, Kanami?
Dad was here with you, right?!
You wanna stay here with Dad, right?!
I...
I like the other Papa better.
Why?
Why is this happening to me?
Hey!
Yes?
Explain this bank transfer.
Huh?
What is this?
That's what I'm asking you!
Why'd you send some random
account 50 million yen?!
I don't recall doing that.
Look, the logs say it was from your PC!
Huh?
That can't be right.
Seriously?
I was deemed to have embezzled
company money and fired on the spot.
Mika used that as an excuse
to file for divorce,
get full custody of Kanami,
and demand child support from me.
What are you doing, newbie?!
I-I'm sorry!
The company and I settled on
me paying back the money lost.
I avoided getting sued, but...
When am I ever gonna pay all that back?
Nitta-kun?
Message
Nitta
"Senpai!
The upcoming 8K remaster box set of RoboKaiser
includes the legendary unaired 12th
episode. I preordered it immediately."
Oh, they're releasing episode 12, huh?
That's awesome.
I've always wanted to watch it.
Let's watch it together once you get it.
If I work hard,
I'm sure things will get better.
And I'll get to see Kanami again, too.
I know she's not even my child...
But still, I believe that my
sacrifices will be rewarded.
I can't afford treatment.
I don't have insurance.
I have no way to borrow money,
and even if I found a way,
I couldn't pay it back.
Don't people say that your old pets come
pick you up when you're about to die?
I wonder if it'll come for me.
What the...?
A dream?
What are you doing with my PC?
Return
Send
Sending 50 million yen?
No way...
The chief did it?
What's with her, dining at an
expensive restaurant and all?
The man she had an affair with,
Kanami's father...
was the chief?!
You're an awful woman.
You foist all that debt
onto your ex-husband,
and you make him pay child support too.
He got to marry and live with me.
It's the least he could do.
Let him make that money back.
It's all he's good for.
What a piece of work.
Kanami's not even his child.
I only wanted superior genes.
I didn't need a kid with a man like him.
Whoo, you're a scary one.
What the hell? What the hell is all this?
Am I dreaming? Please tell me
this is all just a bad dream...
Nay, this is reality.
It's the truth, and nothing but the truth.
You lived such a hard life,
working yourself to the bone...
Yet all this time, it was nothing but lies!
Can they really get away with such evil?
No... I can't let them get away with it!
I'll get my revenge on them.
I'll get them, I swear!
Ah, such purity of emotion.
Rage, hatred, and sorrow!
It's so tasty!
Who the hell are you?
I have taken an interest in you
because you're a good man.
Screw that.
Look what living like a good man has gotten me.
I should've said screw everyone else and
sought my own happiness above all else.
Good karma isn't worth shit.
It's all hogwash.
Wonderful! Truly wonderful!
If I can have a second life,
I wanna do whatever the hell I want.
Hell, I'll live for myself as a villain
who walks all over everyone else.
Boy, do I have some good news for you.
I'm here to send you to another life.
You may call me your guide, if you like.
I've brought you gifts.
How would you like to be reincarnated
in a different world?!
A fantasy world with swords and magic.
A world like this one, but with superpowers.
A period drama!
The wild west!
The Jurassic era.
I've prepared all kinds of options for you!
Reincarnated in another world?
Is this what Nitta-kun was talking about?
I thought this only happened in books.
But it's real?
Now, go ahead and choose
whatever world you like!
Robots and space battleships?
Nitta-kun and I used to
talk about that...
And it was fun.
We'd kick up a real storm talking about it.
A sci-fi fantasy world with both
advanced science and magic.
Feudalism lives strong, and the world's
ruled by royals and their nobles.
I'll make it so you're born into the
house of a count who rules a planet.
A count? That's pretty high up.
So you've made your peace?
I hope you'll have a good life this time, then!
I've had enough of living an honest life.
If I'm being born into nobility,
then screw everyone else,
I'll put my happiness first
and do what I want...
I'll rule with an iron fist
and be as evil as I please!
Oh, this is fun!
Bullying the weak just feels so, so good!
No... Spare me!
Give me more... Entertain me more!
Entertain your evil lord,
the great Liam Sera Banfield!
Revenge
I'm the Evil Lord of
an Intergalactic Empire!
Rebirth
Allow me to show you to... "Rebirth."